□ (+82) 10-4126-7153 | ■ jaywonchung@snu.ac.kr | ♣ jaewonchung.me | □ jaywonchung

Summary_

I am a senior student majoring Electrical and Computer Engineering at Seoul National University, South Korea. I am interested in conducting research on or being involved in projects that deal with large-scale or networked computer systems. Being especially interested in deep learning workloads, I follow up on state-of-the-art deep learning research during my free time. I seek to apply for a Ph.D. position in the USA late this year.

Education

Seoul National University

Seoul, South Korea

B.S. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

2015 - Present

• Current GPA: 4.07/4.3 (overall) 4.13/4.3 (major)

Research Experience

Virtual Machine and Optimization Lab

SNU, South Korea Dec 2019 - Jun 2020

SENIOR PROJECT

· Distributed DNN inference, Mobile Computing

- Worked with Professor Soo-Mook Moon on developing distributed DNN inferences schemes.
- Proposed a distributed video DNN inference scheme that drastically reduces network traffic by exploiting intermittent knowledge distillation.
- Implemented the scheme with PyTorch and OpenMPI with an NVIDIA Jetson Nano embedded board as the client and conducted evaluation.

Computer Vision Lab SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

- Meta-learning, Few-shot Classification
- Conducted research on better meta-initialization points for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning (MAML) using an LSTM-based neural memory.
- · Conducted research on generating task-aware class embeddings to augment feature maps of MAML by formulating a convex program (DPP).

Lab of Imaging Science and Technology

SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping (QSM), Deep Learning
- · Worked with Professor Jongho Lee and submitted our solution to the QSM challenge held by the 5th International Workshop on MRI Phase Contrast and QSM.
- · Designed, implemented, and trained a U-Net variant on in-vivo brain MRI field images and their COSMOS results.

Extracurricular Activity _____

Deepest SNU, South Korea

MEMBER

Dec 2018 - Present

- A free research group on all domains of deep learning. Aggregates researchers from both academia and industry with various backgrounds.
- · Gained experience extensively in computer vision and meta-learning, and attended talks on computer vision, natural language processing, reinforcement learning, and speech recognition.
- Gave a talk with the title "Meta-Learning plus Memory".

Coursera Global Translator Community

translate-coursera.org

LANGUAGE COORDINATOR

Oct 2018 - Present

- Served as Language Coordinator, a selected position that reviews and confirms works by other translators.
- · Created Korean subtitles for Coursera Lectures initially provided only in English. Focused on courses related to machine learning.

Skills

Programming Python, PyTorch, C++, C, MATLAB, JavaScript, LaTeX

English Perfect score on both TOEFL (Feb 2020) and TOEIC (Oct 2018)

Publications

ShadowTutor: Distibuted Partial Distillation for Mobile Video DNN Inference, arXiv:2003.10735 (under review at ICPP 2020)

MARCH 26, 2020 JAEWON CHUNG · RÉSUMÉ